Leslie Torres

661-390-8340 ♦ leslietorres86@gmail.com

-Professional Summary -

Ambitious and goal driven operations and accounting professional offering 8+ years of experience in operations and accounting. Demonstrated ability in providing exceptional leadership skills, developing new processes and procedures across a variety of departments. Well versed in project and time management skills such as prioritizing tasks, multi tasking and delegation of duties. Working from home gave me the ability to work with minimal to no supervision.

- Core Strengths -

- Accounting
- Create a positive work environment
- Decision making skills
- •Excellent communication skills
- Operations
- •Process Improvement
- Self Disciplined
- Team Leadership & Motivation
- •Quick Learner

-Professional Experience-

Office Manager

Oramedix

- Manager (1-15 Employees)
- Accounts Receivables
- Accounts Payable
- Collections
- Billing

- Audit daily sales
- Payroll
- Order Entry
- Assigning and monitoring clerical functions

2/2020- Current

- Supervise Staff
- Design and implement office policies
- Coaching, counseling and disciplining employees
- Tracking budget expenses

Billing and Collections Manager

National Apartment Flooring

- Accounts Payable
- Accounts Receivables
- Collections
- Order Entry
- Billing

- •Job Cost
- Payroll
- Executive Assistant
- •Commercial Project Assistant
- Measure Floor Plans

- 6/2011-9/2019
- Compose Quotes
- •Inspect Properties
- Manager (5-6 employees)
- Audit margins and profits
- Contact 100+ installers daily

Leslie Torres

661-390-8340 ♦ leslietorres86@gmail.com

Digital Global Accounting

1/2009-7/2010

Receptionist/Administrative Assistant

• Coordinate meetings

• Market research

Presentations

• Travel arrangements

Production sales

•Data Entry

Advertise

•Generate reports

Payroll

-Education-

Accounting I&II Certificate

8/2010-5/2011

Abram Friedman Occupational Center

Computer Business Specialist

6/2011-9/2011

American Career College

Real Estate License

10/2019-2/2020

Allied Real Estate School

-References-

Viridiana Acosta

Mavel Dinkane

AnneMarie Diaz

Commercial Project Coordinator

Payroll Specialist

Teacher

(408)375-5090

(424)341-9481

(323)810-0922